Bubbles rise through a murky, golden fluid. Two humanoid figures, formed of glowing yellow energy, step out of the haze.
They gaze into a cylindrical glass tank.
Inside, a mechanical, insectoid creature hangs suspended by cables.
A flash of white light reveals a massive, dark red, metallic Craver. It hangs upside down in a drop bay, its red eye glowing.
It is one of hundreds, suspended in tight rows.
Bay doors slide open beneath them, revealing a desert landscape far below. The Cravers detach and plummet.
From orbit, dozens of drop pods streak toward the planet.
They punch through the clouds, hurtling toward the arid ground.
A massive shockwave spreads across the desert from the impact.
Through a red targeting reticle, Cravers swarm a dusty battlefield, firing on robotic enemies.
An explosion washes everything in white light. The reticle glitches and fades.
In the darkness of night, small fires burn among the jagged, smoking ruins of a destroyed city.
High above the silhouetted wreckage, a blinding, golden light tears across the starry sky.
The light fades into absolute darkness.